ANDRES BARILIN

FRONT-END DEVELOPER

+54 3584235967

victor.barilin@gmail.com

Río Cuarto, Córdoba, Argentina

https://www.victorbarilin.com

SKILLS

- Web Developer
- Mobile Developer
- SCRUM
- Empathy
- Good teamwork
- · Passion for technology

EDUCATION

Platzi 2022 - Current Web Platform

• Software developer

ITec 2020 - 2021 Rio Cuarto city

· Software developer

LANGUEGE

- · Native Spanish
- · Basic English

PROFILE

I'm an Argentine professional willing to relocate, specialized as a front-end developer in tools such as JavaScript, React.js, and React Native, with experience in agile methodology SCRUM. I'm passionate about technologies and I'm constantly learning. Currently, I'm adding Next.js, TypeScript, and MongoDB to my technical skills.

EXPERIENCE

Software Developer

2022 - Current

Ditec (Rio cuarto)

Currently, I work as a Front-end software developer using React.js at this company. I have also worked on projects using React Native. During my time here, my main project has been developing an e-commerce platform for a US-based company called "BuckedUp".

technological development

2020 - 2022

ArboT (Rio Cuarto)

At this company, I performed tasks in both software and hardware. ArboT was a company specialized in robotics development, and my responsibilities were varied, including tasks ranging from 3D design, basic electronics, and problem-solving, to device assembly and programming.